Benjamin Luft collection of 9-11 first responders' oral histories
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Published Materials, 2011 through 2013
  - Teaching aid videos
    The videos are compilations of interview segments pertaining to each video's theme. The videos were at one time hosted on the project's website, www.911respondersremember.org.
    - Legal, Political, & Social Aspects of WTC Disaster, Legal, Political, & Social Aspects of WTC Disaster.mov
    - Personal & Spiritual Impact of WTC Disaster, Personal & Spiritual Impact of WTC Disaster.mov
    - PTSD & Physical Health Symptoms of WTC Disaster, PTSD & Physical Health Symptoms of WTC Disaster.mov
    - Toxic and Traumatic Effects of WTC Disaster, Toxic and Traumatic Effects of WTC Disaster.mov
  - We're Not Leaving book, 2011, We're Not Leaving_FINAL BOOK FILES.pdf
    Digital copy of Dr. Luft's book of project interview excerpts (https://lccn.loc.gov/2012358325). The introduction and acknowledgements contain some background information about Luft and the 9/11 oral history project.